darkness hovers above us
you can feel it but you cannot see it
because a god has been summoned that
cancel god
the canceled god wants to cancel you
that wants to cancel everyone you know
it wants to cancel humanity itself
we felt that putting this in a
mythological
story structure would give it a
different
angle to consider the concept so right
now for whatever reason cancel culture
is the the hot meme that a lot of people
are talking about
and it feels right to release something
to have an original take on it
uh that will give pause to people when
they're
you know arguing about uh should cancel
culture be a thing or it's not a thing
and think about sort of the on an
energetic level on a spiritual level
what is occurring so the cancer god has
one goal
and that is to cancel humanity itself
the cancer god doesn't give a shit
about being woke doesn't care about your
political
ideologies uh it has one goal it's just
to cancel all of us
the idea with cancer culture is
get the word cancellation you're
cancelled
and with that there's no room for for
dialogue there's no room for nuance
there's no room for
redemption most importantly and in order
to cancel problematic ideas
you cancel people who hold those
problematic ideas
and the idea there is you view them as
inherently problematic you view them as
evil
and there's a sense of hatred there's a
sense of
anger intense hatred and anger in a
religious fervor
that comes from this cancellation and
and from that
the being of the canceled god emerged
we felt that the cancer god is
malnourished
that is it is insatiable and that it
eats
truth right it eats the ability to speak
truth by um canceling everyone's ability
to come out into the public
square and speak their truthfulness but
it also speaks to the fact that it is
yeah just deeply malnourished and in
constant want
that it can never be satiated and it's
this
this devouring hole and its chest
um well yeah will never be fed
until it is all cancelled
[Music]
there is this state of fear that a lot
of people are living in
and i have friends who are in let's say
more centrists
people who are maybe a little bit more
reactionary and i have progressivist
friends too
and across the board across this
political spectrum everyone's afraid of
cancer culture everyone's kind of
stumbling on their words they're
um not sure what they can say so they're
guarding themselves
and so not really fully showing up with
their truth and
that is uh something that i think is
needed is to fully show up with their
truth
and have the courage to be wrong there's
a tragic
component of the adapt of cancel and
that
they continuously project
their own shadow material outwardly
onto their perceived enemies in a way
they're trying to cancel
their own shadow by projecting it onto
these outward enemies
my hope uh and it could be a naive hope
is for this piece to serve as
a psychoactive meme if you will like a
psychoactive drug
that when people see it they'll never
look at cancer culture the same way
again
they will see maybe something else is
going on some kind of dark energy some
dark force
and how this idea of cancer culture has
a nihilistic
energy about it and it just doesn't want
to cancel people who are
not woke or problematic wants to cancel
everyone even people who are woke
yeah i hope for the same and i actually
would like to invite anyone who feels
creatively inspired and urged to
take this further explore it uh cancel
it
anything you want to do as long as it's
creative if there's like a creative way
to cancel this
creative way to cancel us go ahead i
think that again that's that's uh
that's out there as a possibility as we
juggle with
you know content with all these forces
that i think at the end when taking with
truth and honesty
make us better